myadsclassified.com 2018-03-18

# Privacy Policy - Myadsclassified.com

**

Privacy Policy

**

We take your right to privacy seriously and we want you to feel comfortable using our web site. This Privacy Policy deals with personally identifiable information (referred to as "Data" below) that may be collected by us on our site. This Policy does not apply to other entities that we do not own or control or persons that are not our employees, agents or within our control. Please take time to read our Terms of Use.

Myadsclassified.com is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Myadsclassified.com and governs data collection and usage. By using the Myadsclassified.com, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**

Cookies

**

Like many web sites, we set and use cookies to enhance your user experience, such as retaining your personal settings. Advertisements may appear on our web site and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer and is subject to the privacy policy of those parties providing the advertisement.

The Myadsclassified.com use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Myadsclassified.com pages, or services, a cookie helps Myadsclassified.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Myadsclassified.com, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Myadsclassified.com features that you customized. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Myadsclassified.com services or Web sites you visit.

We do employ cookies. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user's computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable Myadsclassified.com to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users. Our cookies do not have an expiration date. Our cookies do not collect personally identifiable information.

For more information on third-party advertising-related cookies and how to opt-out of them, please visit on of the following third party websites:

Cookie Policy updated 15 April 2014

**

Collection of Data

**

Providing us with other information is at your option. Please take note that your e-mail address, or other submissions that you make on this site may contain your real name or other personally identifiable information and, as a result, may appear on this site. Like many web sites, we may also automatically receive general information that is contained in our server log files such as your IP address and cookie information. Information about how advertising may be served on this site (if at all) is set forth below.

Myadsclassified.com collects information through our Web site at several points. We collect the following information about primary users: Email Address - To verify accounts and allow buyers to contact sellers. Myadsclassified.com does not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child under 13 to divulge personal information. Myadsclassified.com is a child freindly site that actively filters out inappropriate sites. If you know of an inappropriate word or term being used in this site, please contact us at Myadsclassified.com so that we can remove it. Occasionally we collect the following general data that is not personally identifiable information, such as city, age, ethnicity, education, salary, and various others. We occasionally request demographic data in order to understand our site visitors and provide a better, more custom experience. We verify the accuracy of this information by sending follow up emails.

**

Use of Data

**

The information collected by Myadsclassified.com will be used for improving our web site and providing our service. Please be advised that information posted in these venues becomes public knowledge. If our policy on information collection or uses changes, will advise you here. Please be advised. Your Ability to Access, Review and Change your Personal Information. Therefore you must not disclose your Myadsclassified.com information to any third parties.

**

Under 15's.

**

We do not allow persons who are under fifteen (15) years old to use this site.

Myadsclassified.com does not knowingly collect any information from persons under the age of 15. If Myadsclassified.com learns that a posting is by a person under the age of 15, Myadsclassified.com will remove that post.

**

Changes to the Privacy Policy

**

We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. We will notify you of substantial changes to this Policy either by posting a prominent announcement on our site and/or by sending a message to the e-mail address you have provided to us that is contained within your user settings.

As Myadsclassified.com continues to develop, we may add new services and features to our site. In the event that these additions, changes to the law or changes to Myadsclassified.com 's terms of use affect our Privacy Policy, this document will and can be updated when it is appropriated. Your continued use of the web site after the effective date of any changes will constitute your acceptance of all of the changes.

While this Privacy Policy states our standards for maintenance of Data and we will make efforts to meet them, we are not in a position to guarantee these standards. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of data. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of Data.
